A Guide to the Papers of James J. Kilpatrick
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Pon - Pov (Box-folder 41:6)
    Lou Ponder, Edward R. Pongraz, Robert W. Pons, E. Gwinnette Poole, Robert H. Poole Sr., William S. Poole, E.M. Pooley- El Paso Herald-Post, Wallace F. Poore, E.M. Pope, Lonnie H. Pope-Charlottesville Board of Assessors, Margaret Pope, W.B. Pope, John Popham, Barbara G. Porter, C.A. Porterfield, Alan Posner-University of Rochester, Florence Dean Post, Gladys E. Post-American Coalition of Patriotic Societies, Johnetta Poteat, Alden A. Potter, Bill Potter- Frankfort Morning Times,, Gary K. Potter, I. Lee Potter-Republican Party of Virginia, Mrs. Ione S. Potter-Martha Dandridge Women's Club, Walter B. Potter- Culpeper Star-Exponent, Miss J. Potts, Kenneth Potts-Distributive Education Clubs of America, Virginia N. Potts, Ray A.H. Poupore, Shirley Povich
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: Pow - Prince Edward School Foundation (Box-folder 41:7)
    E. Angus Powell, Hugh P. Powell, Hume S. Powell, James M. Powell - The Jefferson Hotel, John C. Powell, Lewis F. Powell Jr., Lewis F. Powell Sr., Rear Admiral Paulus P. Powell, Robert J. Powell, Marie Power, Olney Hume Powers Jr., William A. Powers, Vicci Pownall, Prague Newsletter, L.G. Pratt, Barbara Preddy, T.K. Preddy, Albert Moore Prendergast, Mrs. M. Presnell, Press, Elmer E. Preston, Mrs. Howard H. (Lucy) Preston, W.R. Preston-WRVA TV, Laurence A. Price-Smith and Kline French Laboratories, Mrs. Robert C. (Betty R.) Price, Matthew Priestly, W.L. Prieur Jr.-Corporate Court of Norfolk, Edward A. Prill, Hal G. Prillaman-Martinsville Junior Chamber of Commerce (Jaycees), Prince Edward School Foundation
  - 1956-1961 Correspondence: Burton A. Prince (Box-folder 42:1)
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Prince, G - End P (Box-folder 42:2)
    George N. Prince, Lillian Pringle, Nathalie Marie Prise, Bernice Proctor, Robert Proddow Jr.-Navy League of the United States, John A. Proffitt Jr., Progress Index, Progressive Architecture, Mrs. Russell Prosser, Thomas T. Prousalis, Hazel Prout, Provost - Richmond Professional Institute, Bernard Prushan-Vantage Press, Publisher's Weekly, H. Lamont Pugh MD, Jesse F. Pugh, Jordan A. Pugh III, Katie Pugh-Personal Improvement Course, Rev. Thomas E. Pugh-Williamsburg Baptist Church, Pulitzer Prize Awards Committee, F. Bert Pulley, Eugene S. Pulliam- The Indianapolis Star, Spencer M. Punnett, Griffith Purcell, T.M. Purcell Jr., Thomas W. Purcell Jr., Lt. Col. W. Griffith Purcell, Merlo J. Pusey- The Washington Post, William A. Pusey - The Reading Guide-University of Virginia School of Law, William C. Pusey, Carleton Putnam, Lacey E. Putney, Durwood T. Pye-Georgia Commission on Education, Harold G. Pyle
  - 1962-1965 Correspondence: Carleton Putnam (Box-folder 42:3)
  - 1949-1953, n.d. Correspondence - Public Utilities Fortnightly (Box-folder 42:4)
  - 1956-1963 Correspondence - Q (Box-folder 42:5)
    Ruth Quann, Lawrence R. Quarles-University of Virginia Dean of Engineering, Miriam Quarles-Carolina Power and Light Company, August W. Quattrochi-Western Reserve University, William W. Quay, Evelyn Byrd Jervey Quinlivan, I.T. Quinn, Jim Quinn, Susan Quinn - The Pan-American School, Charles L. Quittmeyer-University of Buffalo School of Business
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Rabb - Ratcliffe (Box-folder 42:6)
    Russell L. Rabb-Better Business Bureau, Clarence E. Rabinow-King Features Syndicate, Frederick A. Rabor Jr., Ed Rachels-Seaboard Airline Railroad Company, J.E. Radcliffe, Radford College, P.S. Radman, Col. Paul Howard Rafferty-ALMC-ASMC, W.J. Raftery Jr., Anne Raidabaugh- Southern Accent, Annielee Raiford, Richard E. Railey, Hon. William Rainach, John E. Raine-Commission on the Aging, Mrs. R.C. Randall, Beverley H. Randolph, Frank S. Randolph, John H. Randolph, Robert M. Randolph, Theodore F. Randolph, Vergil P. Randolph, E.L. Rankin Jr.-Office of the Governor of North Carolina, M.G. Ramey-Lion's Club, John Spruell Ramos, Ramrus-Producer- The Mike Wallace Interview, Andrew Ramsay, W.S. Ramseur, Walter G. Ramseur, E.W. Ramsey, Horace W. Raper-Tennessee Technology University, Laura D. Ratchford, Lydia Ratcliff, Clyde Ratcliffe
  - 1956-1965 Correspondence: Jack Rathbone (Box-folder 42:7)
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: Rati - Red (Box-folder 42:8)
    Ion Ratiu, J.A. Ratta Jr., Mrs. Benjamin Thomas Rauber, Fritz Rauschenberg, Mrs. Benjamin Watlins Rawles, Heath J. Rawley, James A. Rawley-Sweet Briar College, James A. Rawley, James Scott Rawlings, Sen. William V. Rawlings-5 th District, Capt. George J. Rawlins-USA, James R. Ray, Ramona Ray, Rita F. Ray, Wisner Ray, Robert Raynolds, Irene Raysman, Frances Owen Rea, J.A. Read, Leonard E. Read-Foundation for Economic Education, Reader's Digest, Jere Real- Campus Conservative, Michael T. Reardon, Research Institute of America, Fred H. Reaves, Laurie Reaves, Marcel Reboussin-College of William and Mary, Prof. Wilson Record-Sacramento State College, Recreation, Mrs. John W. Red, Joseph R. Redding D.C.-Florida Pure Water Association, William H. Redfern Jr.-St. Andrews Presbyterian College, Charles R. Redford, Redistricting, John Redmond
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Reed - Regi (Box-folder 43:1)
    A. Reed, Arthur Reed, Henry Hope Reed, K. Terrence Reed-State University of Iowa, Philip G. Reed Register and Tribune Syndicate, William T. (Billy) Reed Jr., Walter Reed, Mrs. W.J. (Grace) Reedy, Agnes B. Reese, Dr. C.B. Reese, Mrs. W.H. Reese Jr., Lew P. Reeve, Col. A.R. Reeves U.S.A. (Ret.), Judge Albert L. Reeves-Senior U.S. District Judge, Adm. J.W. Reeves Jr. U.S.N. (Ret.), Col. Le Roy Reeves-The Army and Navy Club, Mrs. Charles E. Regester, Walter W. Regirer-Virginia Association of Nursing Homes-Neighborhood Improvement Association-Virginia State Bar
  - 1955-1966 Correspondence: Henry Regnery-Publisher (Box-folder 43:2)
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Reh - Rey (Box-folder 43:3)
    George T. Rehberg- Fore America, Ad. G.Reich, Mary Sue Reichert, Mrs. Henry J. Reichman, Legh W. Reid, Wallace Reid, Mrs. William F. Reid, Charles Reilly- Norfolk Ledger-Star, Georgia Reimer, Donald K. Reiner, Robert D. Reinhardt, Mrs. J.D. Reisser, Religious Matters, Florence Remington, Mrs. R.C. (Gladys L.) Remington - Medical College of Virginia Hospital, Werner Renberg- Business Week, James G. Rennie - Virginia Dairy Company, Edmund A. Rennolds Jr.-Branch and Company, Seymour Rennolds, Dave Rensberger, H.W. Repass, The Republic and Gazette, Republican District Headquarters, Republican Party of Virginia, Reston Virginia, Beryl L. Reubens-Brandeis University, Dean H.G. Reuschlein-Villanova University, J.G. Reveley, Edna C. Rex, Frances L. Rex-Richmond Artists Association, C.M. Reynolds, Mrs. Charles W. Reynolds, George A. Reynolds M.D., Hannah C. Reynolds, J. Louis Reynolds-Eskimo Pie Corporation, J. Owen Reynolds, J. Sargeant Reynolds, Jesse Reynolds-Department of Parks and Recreation-The Mosque, R.S. Reynolds Jr.-Reynolds Metal Company, Victor Reynolds-University Press of Virginia, William H. Reynolds
  - 1965-1967 Correspondence: Anne Rentz (Box-folder 43:4)
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Rh - Richardson (Box-folder 43:5)
    Lucius Rhind, W.S. Rhoads Jr.-Miller and Rhoads, Dr. Joseph G. Rhode, John Q. Rhodes Jr., W. Edgar Rhodes, William H. Rhodes, S. White Rhyne, Jr., Dean F.D.G. Ribble-University of Virginia School of Law, Jackson Ricau-The Citizen's Report, Adolph Rice, Arthur H. Rice- The Nation's Schools, Arthur W. Rice, Barbara S. Rice-Houghton Mifflin Company, Charles E. Rice -Conservative Party of New York State, Charles Page Rice, Eva Rice -Utah Citizen's Committee Against Flouridation, Mrs. Greek Polan Rice, J. Linwood Rice-State Fair of Virginia, J.W. Rice-Ordnance Research Laboratory, Lee Rice, Leslie Rice, Nolan E. Rice - University of Richmond, P.A. Rice, W. Nelson Rump-American Airlines, W. Thomas Rice- Atlantic Coast Line, Elsie Rich, Charles W. Richards, G.H. Richards, Gertrude Richards, William R. Richards, Don Richardson- Christian Science Monitor, Mrs. E.L. Richardson M.D.-F.A.C.S., Mrs. H.D. Richardson, J.S. Richardson, John Richardson Jr., John C. Richardson, Mabel M. Richardson, Mrs. Ralph M. Richardson, Warren S. Richardson
  - 1955-1957 Correspondence: Donald R. Richberg (Box-folder 43:6)
  - 1955-1966 Correspondence: Richey - Rider (Box-folder 43:7)
    Homer Richey, City of Richmond, "Richmond Afternoons", Richmond Area Community Council, Richmond Area Safety Council, Richmond Artists Association, Richmond Braves, Richmond Camellia Society Members, Richmond Council of Garden Clubs, Richmond International Council, Richmond Professional Institute, Richmond Public Library, Richmond Public Schools, Richmond Rebels, Richmond Symphony, Charles C. Richmond, Mrs. H.S. Richmond, Elihu Richter M.D.-Medical College of Virginia, Elizabeth N. Richter, F.C. Richter Jr. - Virginia-Carolina Chemical Corporation, William F. Rickenbacker, Charles Rickman-Age 12, Katharine C. Ricks, Margaret P. Ricks, R.A. Ricks, W.T. Riddel, C.B. Riddle, Lloyd S. Riddle, Jack Rider - Lenoir County News, M.C. Rider, Richard Rider
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: N. Cowl Rider (Box-folder 44:1)
  - 1956-1965 Correspondence: Rider - Roanoke (Box-folder 44:2)
    Wilber J. Rider-Lenoir County News Company, W.C. Ridgway, Walter L. Riedy, John W. Riely, Geraldine Riffenburgh, J.S. Riggan-Sea Board Airline Railroad, Mrs. R.P. Riggan, Allan E. Riggin, J.F. Rigsby, Juanita Rigsby, Eleanor Rikard, Mrs. M.O. Rike, Jr., C.B. Riley, Jack Riley-Carolina Power and Light Company, Paul Ringler- The Milwuakee Journal- Milwaukee Journal-Sentinel, Eugene F. Rinta-Counsel of State Chambers of Commerce, George G. Ritchie Jr. M.D.-Christian Youth Corps of America, Robert Ritchie, L.M. Ritter, Prof. Wilfred J. Ritz-Washington and Lee University School of Law, Frank G. Rivera, J.R.T. Rives, Leo A. Roach, Mrs. Obie Lewis Roach, Mrs. Robert Roadcap Jr., S.P. Roane, Roanoke World News
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Robb-A.D. Robertson (Box-folder 44:3)
    Clarke T. Robb, Jessie M. Robb, Gus Robbins- The Hopewell News, Adm. Thomas H. Robbins Jr.-Naval War College, Louis Robert, Paul Robert, Allen E. Roberts, Major Arch E. Roberts U.S.A.R., Bill Roberts, Bob Roberts, David Roberts, Elizabeth Roberts, James W. Roberts-House of Delegates-Virginia, L.J. Roberts, Owen J. Roberts-Atlantic Union Committee, Ruby Altizer Roberts- The Lyric, A.D. Robertson
  - 1951-1958 Correspondence: Senator A. Willis Robertson (Box-folder 44:4)
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: Robertson - Robinson (Box-folder 44:5)
    Archibald G. Robertson, Brenda Robertson, Doug Robertson-Virginia State Penitentiary, E.C. Robertson, George Alex Robertson, Hugh Robertson, Mrs. John A. Robertson, Kenneth Douglas Robertson Jr., L.R. Robertson, Mrs. Maude Robertson, Reese S. Robertson, W.B. Robertson, Walter S. Robertson-Assistant Secretary of State for Far Eastern Affairs, Gertrude James Robey, Berkeley Robins, E. Claiborne Robins-A.H. Robins Company, R.B. Robins, Albert D. Robinson, Lt. Col. C.O. Robinson, Dale G. Robinson-University of Richmond, E. Emma Robinson, J. Hall Robinson, J.T. Robinson, M.A. Robinson, Sam Robinson, W.D. Robinson, William M. Robinson Jr.
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Rock - Rogers (Box-folder 44:6)
    Rock Hill Academy, John Delaney Rock-Traffic Department-Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, Edward Arthur Rockwood, Fred W. Rodgers, G.T. Rodgers-Chrisholm Elementary School, Bertram Rodman-Temple Mishkan Tefila Forum, Charles H. Roe, Lois Roehr, John C. Rogers, L.F. Rogers, Marian Rogers
  - 1950-1960, n.d. Correspondence - George W. Rogers (Box-folder 44:7)
  - 1951 Correspondence: Silas Rogers (Box-folder 44:8)
  - 1952 Correspondence: Silas Rogers (Box-folder 45:1)
  - 1953-1956 Correspondence: Silas Rogers (Box-folder 45:2)
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Rogg - Rop (Box-folder 45:3)
    Ben A. Rogge, Leo Rogol-Rivermont Church of Christ, G. Frederick Roll-Smith Kline and French Laboratories, Coralyn Roller, Mrs. Howard C. Roller, E.J. Rollings, Albert Rollins-Dalton Georgia City Clerk, Heinz Rollman, George Romney-Governor of Michigan, Col. Warren L. Romans-Department of the Army, John J. Rooney - U.S. Congress, Q. Roos, Archibald B. Roosevelt, Edith Kermit Roosevelt, George C. Roper Jr., William L. Roper
  - 1954-1955 Correspondence: Billy Rose Column-"Pitching Horse Shoes" (Box-folder 45:4)
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Rose - Rouse (Box-folder 45:5)
    D.E. Rose, E.J.B. Rose-International Press Institute, Frances M. Rose, Harold P. Rose, J.T. Rose Sr.-Board of Real Estate Assessors, Louis M. Rose, Marc A. Rose- Reader's Digest, R.H. Rose Jr., Dan Rosenberger Jr., Rosenbloom Case, M.V. Rosenbloom-American Surveys, Jerome Rosenthal, C.A. Ross, Ida Jane Ross-Office of the Hon. Thomas N. Downing, Ivan Ross, Matilda Ross, William P. Ross, Charlie Rosson, Irwin Rosten-Wolper Productions, Leo Rosten-Cowles Magazines, Inc., William Rostron, The Rotarian, Fred H. Roth-City Charter Committee, Anne B. Roundtree-Lakeview Clinic, Martha Roundtree, L.C. Rouse, Parke Rouse-Jamestown Festival Commission
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Rowan - Royston (Box-folder 45:6)
    Arch H. Rowan, A. Prescott Rowe-Central Virginia Educational Television Corporation, Charles S. Rowe- The Freelance-Star, Dan M. Rowe, Edith L. Rowe, Harry Rowe, Maurice B. Rowe-Acting Commissioner of Agriculture, T. Kenneth Rowe, David Rowland-Lynchburg Public Library, Koil Rowland, Mrs. P.L. Rowlett, Russell J. Rowlett Jr.-Virginia-Carolina Chemical Corporation, Evelyn Harding Rowzie, E.A. Roy, Margaret Shaw Royall, John B. Royer, Robert D. Royer-Reynolds Metals Company, Mrs. A. Royster, Bernard L. Royster Jr.-YMCA, Vermont Royster- Wall Street Journal, Grandison D. Royston Jr.- The Hopkins Review - Johns Hopkins University
  - 1950-1955 Correspondence: Louis D. Rubin, Jr. (Box-folder 45:7)
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Louis D. Rubin, Jr. (Box-folder 45:8)
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Rucker - Rundle (Box-folder 46:1)
    Ed H. Rucker-Richmond Dairy Co., Katharine Wood Rucker, Andrew Ruckman II- The Cavalier Daily, Miles Rudisill Jr., D. Rudolph, J. Randolph Ruffin-Colonial Williamsburg, Thomas L. Ruffin, William B. Ruggles- The Dallas Morning News, Edward A. Rumely-Committee for Constitutional Government, Edward A. Rumely, L.A. Rundle
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Rusher - End "R" (Box-folder 46:2)
    William A. Rusher- National Review, Hon. Dean Rusk-Secretary of State, Anna Russell, Barbara C. Russell, John Russell, Most Reverend John J. Russell, Mr. and Mrs. Walter Russell-University of Science and Philosophy, Milton C. Russell-Virginia State Library, Randolph Russell, Richard B. Russell-U.S. Senate, Virginia Hansford Russell, W.H. Russell, Charles A. Russo, Tom Rutherford, Mrs. G.A. Rutledge, Dave Ryan, James N. Ryan, Walter Rybeck- Dayton Daily News, David Warren Ryder, Richard R. Ryder, J. Oskar Rydstrom, Quincy Ryland, W. Bradford Ryland, Gary Lyons, Allan H. Ryskind- Human Events, Morrie Ryskind Column
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Sa - San (Box-folder 46:3)
    Karl A. Sack, J.M. Sacks, Stanley E. Sacks-Virginia House of Delegates, Marsha Sacre, George W. Sadler-Richmond City Council, Harold R. Sadler, Rose Sadowsky, Ruth Perkins Safford, Saint Bridget's Parent-Teacher Association, William T. St. Clair, Richard S. Salant-CBS News, Thomas Raysor Salley Jr., Marion H. Salmon, Mrs. John Salsbury, Karen Salvatore, Ed Salzbech, G.E. Sams, Richard F. Sams, Mrs. W.M. Samuel, Mrs. M. Samuels, San Marino Tribune, Grace Sanchez-Salazar and Maureen Shea, John F. Sanderford Jr., Rev. Herbert W. Sanders-U.S. Army, Hope Sanders-Photo Maxima, Lewis Sanders, Paul H. Sanders- Race Relations Law Reporter-Vanderbilt University, Mrs. Hal Sandy, Terry Sanford, Richard P. Sanger - Wilmington Morning News, William T. Sanger-Invitation Committee-Medical College of Virginia Station, J. Conrad Sankpill, Clark Santini-Travis Student Union - University of Nevada
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Sar - Sas (Box-folder 46:4)
    Mike Sarco, Dwight E. Sargent- The Portland Press-Herald- New York Herald-Tribune, Reed Sarratt-Southern Education Reporting Service-Southern Regional Education Board- Winston-Salem Journal and Sentinel, Adrian Waldo Sasha-Living Knowledge Foundation, Marion Hutson Sass -Office of the Hon. Strom Thurmond
  - 1940-1967 Correspondence: Sat - Schl (Box-folder 46:5)
    Hon. David E. Satterfield Jr.-House of Representatives, Mr. and Mrs. David E. Satterfield III, Saturday Review, Stephen B. Satz, Mrs. J.T. Sauerbier, J.D. Saumweber-Sperry Piedmont Company, A.D. Saunders, J.W. Saunders, Ray Saunders III, Paul Saunier Jr.-Secretary to J. Vaughn Gary - U.S. Congress, James N. Savadge, Francis Savage, George W. Sawyer - Outdoor Advertising Association, James H. Saxon-Ashland Presbyterian Church, Patrick F. Scanlan- The Tablet, Victor K. Scavullo-Legion Utensils Company, Mrs. Alfred B. Schad-Richmond Council of Garden Clubs, Lois Schaedle, Walter L. Schaffer, Albert Schatz-Washington University, Schedules-Washington to Richmond, J.J. Scherer Jr., Lewis M. Scherer Jr.-Sheraton Park Hotel, Lois G. Schermerhorn, Richard W. Schetter, Florence E. Schiele, Dr. A.M. Schierholz-chiropractor, Mrs. Ross P. Schlabach, Clarence O. Schlaver- The Quill, Thomas B. Schlesinger, Urban Schlitz
  - 1952-1966 Correspondence: Paul Saunier Jr. (Box-folder 46:6)
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Schm - Schw (Box-folder 46:7)
    Emerson P. Schmidt-Economic Research Department-U.S. Chamber of Commerce, G.H.W. Schmidt-Governor's Advisory Committee on Decent Literature, Richard E. Schmidt-Micro Photo, Richard J. Schmidt, Alfred J. Schmitt Jr., Dr. Allen M. Schmuller-Northern Illinois University, Mary Schneider, J.W. Schoch, F.G. Schonbert-Sanborn Map Company, School Executive, Mrs. Walter P. Schoonaur, Andrew James Schorr, Donald N. Schorr-International Association for the Advancement of Ethnology and Eugenics, Paul H. Schrodt, Anna Schroeder, C. Schroeder, Dr. Albert Schrut, Elliott W. Schryver - Doubleday and Company, Robert Lindsay Schuettinger, Mrs. S. Schulberg, Loring Schuler-National Associated Businessmen, Michael Schuller-Constitution Society of Ohio, Rabbi Benjamin Schultz - American Jewish League Against Communism, Charles M. Schulz- Peanuts, Mrs. D. Schuringa-Citizens Against Flouridation, George S. Schuyler, Mrs. Lambert Schuyler, Robert C. Schwab, Jim Schwaninger- Missouri Press News, Blanche G. Schwartz, Edward P. Schwartz, Joyce A. Schwartz, William Schwartz, Ted Schwarz, W. Harry Schwarzschild Jr.-Central National Bank, Albert L. Schweitzer - St. Louis Post- Dispatch, Egon Schwelb-Division of Human Rights-United Nations, Alfred J. Schweppe- American Bar Association Journal, Kurt Schwerin-Northern University School of Law Library
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Sco - Scr (Box-folder 46:8)
    Fon H. Scofield Jr.-Southern Baptist Convention, Adrian H. Scolten M.D., Rose Scorgie, Scott, Foresman and Company, A.B. Scott, George Cole Scott-Scout-O-Rama, Glenn Allen Scott- Norfolk Virginian-Pilot, Herschel N. Scott-Citizens for Goldwater-Miller, Horace H. Scott-Right Worthy Grand Council, James H. Scott, Mary Wingfield Scott, Mrs. R.G. Scott, R.K. Scott-All American Books-America's Future, R.T. Scott-Virginia Paper Company, Robert T. Scott, Ruth Scott, Sidney Buford and Buford Scott-Medical College of Virginia Foundation, Venora M.B. Scott, William D. Scott, Bernice J. Scroggins, Philip L. Scruggs
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Scu - Se (Box-folder 47:1)
    Dr. John Scudder-The Presbyterian Hospital, Vincent Scully, Claudia Scurlock, Nancy Seaman, Mrs. D. Scott (Betty) Sears, Capt. Bill Seawell Sr., C.P. Seay - The Bulletin -Southern Railway System, Mrs. Richmond Seay, David Sebra, Anna Sects, Francis Minturn Sedgwick, Mary Seely, J.C. Seidel-New York State Division of Housing, R.S. Seidensticker-Larus and Brother Company Tobacco Manufacturers, Harry W. Selden, J.Sinclair Selden Jr.-Kiwanis International, Mrs. Murrell Gail Selden Jr., Joan Joyce Sellers, Meb Segrest, John F. Segrest Jr., Mrs. Walter M. Sehnert, Mrs. Harry (Hattie) Semones, Helen R. Seniunas, Thurman Sensing-Southern States Industrial Council, Theodore A. Serrill - Pennsylvania Society of Newspaper Editors, George W. Settle Jr. - Virginia Office of the Comptroller, William F. Settles, William H. Seward, Charles Eli Sexton
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence - Sha (Box-folder 47:2)
    Mrs. E. Donald Shackelford, Jack S. Shackleton, Virginia J. Shackleton, Evalyn W. Shaed, Mrs. Zillah H. Schafer, John J. Shaffer Jr.-Thomson Machinery Company, H.D. Shamblin, Gadsden E. Shand Jr., William R. Shands, Edgar M. Shaner, Mack I. Shanholtz M.D. - Virginia Department of Health, George E. Shank Jr., Lt. Col. Oliver D. Shank-U.S.A. (ret.), Dr. Edgar F. Shannon Jr.-President - University of Virginia, George W. Shannon- Shreveport Journal, L.D. Shannon Jr., Dr. Jerome Shapiro, Chandar Dhar Sharma-Central Potato Research Institute - Simla India, Louis J. Sharp-Administrative Office of the United States Courts, Philip D. Sharp Jr.-Washington and Lee University - Mock Republican National Convention, Robert M. Sharp-Neighborhood Improvement Association, Constance Sharpe, Hariet Gunn Sharwood - Albemarle Chapter-Daughters of the American Revolution, Mrs. E.D. Shaver-Richmond Council of Women's Organizations, William Russ Shaver, Mrs. Cleo Shaw, Dr. John Allen Shaw, Mimi Shaw-Church Federation of Greater Chicago, Robert B. Shaw, Paul B. Shawen
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: She - Shel (Box-folder 47:3)
    John Shea Jr., Michael J. Shea, Thomas L. Shean Jr.-Providence College, Don P. Shearer, Harold P. Sheehan, Mrs. William F. Sheehan, Vernon Sheeley, Rev. L.F. Sheen, Rev. Charles W. Sheerin Jr. - Bruton Parish Church, Rev. Clarence Levi Shelby M.A.-D.D. Pastor - Westside Presbyterian Church, Bill Sheldon-University of Virginia, Courtney P. Sheldon- Christian Science Monitor, E.P. Sheldon, William W. Sheldon, Will Shelelon, Willis Shell-The William Byrd Press, Sheltering Arms Hospital, David R. Shelton, Farrar B. Shelton, James W. Shelton - Realtor, Lloyd Shelton, Lynn Shelton- The Halifax Gazette
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Shen - Shep (Box-folder 47:4)
    Shenandoah-The Washington and Lee University Review, Miley G. Shenk, Eleanor P. Sheppard-Richmond City Council, Mrs. Theodore Sheppard, John Ben Shepperd-Attorney General of Texas-Odessa Natural Gasoline Company, Josephine M. Shepperson-State Fair of Virginia
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Sher - Sho (Box-folder 47:5)
    Mrs. J. Leo Sheran, Sheraton Hotel, E.G. Sherburne Jr.-American Association for the Advancement of Science, Fred G. Sherill, Bill Sherman, Fred G. Sherrill, Capt. Vincent J. Sherry Jr. USAF, Frances Shield, Dr. James Asa Shields-The Tucker Hospital, Murray Shields, Earl J. Shiflet-Agricultural Bureau-Richmond Chamber of Commerce -Virginia Association of Electric Cooperatives, Nellie Brownfield Shiflet-Indiana Institute of Technology, S.E. Shifrin - Intercontinental Features, Emile S. Shihadeh, Robert J. Shine Jr., Gregory E. Shinert, Frances (Fluff) Shinnick- Hollins Columns-Hollins College, W.H. Shirer-Bailey's Supreme Coffee, Elliot M. Shirk-Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry Fair Practice Commission, Frank C. Shirk-Virginia Library Association, Will Shocket-Capitol News Agency, Don Shoemaker-Southern Education Reporting Service - Southern School News- The Miami Herald, Vaughn Shoemaker, J.J. Shomon Virginia Game Commission- Virginia Wildlife, Kenneth Paul Shorey- The University Bookman- The Columbia State, Garry Short- Los Angeles Times Syndicate, Shelton H. Shot III, Martin L. Shotzberger-University of Richmond, John L. Showers-Job de Camp
  - 1955-1967 Correspondence: Shr - Simm (Box-folder 47:6)